(Howard:)Uh, if you ever need
a reference or anything,
(Howard:)just let me know.
(Man:)Hey, guys.
WOMAN:
You made it.
(Sheldon:)Did you see that?
(Sheldon:)He just cut the line.
(Leonard:)He's just joining
his friends; it's fine.
(stammers)
No, it's not fine.
(Sheldon:)It is a breach
of line etiquette.
(Howard:)We're near the front
of the line.
(Howard:)We'll get in either way.
(Sheldon:)What if every person in front
of us lets someone cut?
(Leonard:)We'd still get in.
(Sheldon:)What if each of those people
let someone cut?
(Leonard:)Still get in.
(Sheldon:)But then each of those
people let someone cut?
(Leonard:)We'd still get in,
but first I'd hit you
(Leonard:)over the head
with his stick chair.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
Oh, please don't.
(Sheldon:)Uh, uh, I couldn't
help but notice
(Sheldon:)that you cut the line.
(Man:)Oh, uh, I'm with my friends.
(Man:)It's cool.
(Sheldon:)Well, no.
(Sheldon:)It's not cool.
(Sheldon:)If there were
reserved seating,
(Sheldon:)and we all had tickets,
that would be fine.
(Sheldon:)But this line is
first-come, first-served.
Not “show up tardy and
nevertheless be first served”.
(Sheldon:)Right here.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)You need to go to
the back of the line.
(scoffs)
Uh, who made you line monitor?